Guide to the Bert Hansen Collection of Advertising Fans circa early 20th century-circa 2003 PR 438
New-York Historical Society
- BH-064. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.064)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of a Midwestern farm with wide horizon titled "Tranquil Beauty." Babcock Home Furnishing Centers, New Smyrna Beach, Florida. Printer: Bagley Specialty Advertising, Lakeland, Florida. Various notations were made on the fan.
- BH-065. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.065)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photograph of a lake in the mountains titled "Timberline Lake." Duffy-Behrendt Funeral Home, Pontiac, Illinois, and Watson Funeral Home in Odell, Illinois.
- BH-066. Vintage, circa 1966 (Box 2, Folder BH.066)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of church in rolling landscape titled "Autumn Splendor." Welch's Store, Centennial 1866-1966, Minnesota Lake, Minnesota. Copy 1; see BH-067.
- BH-067. Vintage, circa 1966 (Box 2, Folder BH.067)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of church in rolling landscape titled "Autumn Splendor." Welch's Store, Centennial 1866-1966, Minnesota Lake, Minnesota. Copy 2; see BH-066.
- BH-068. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.068)
  Rounded rectangle. Pink-toned image of little girl dressed for church, holding a New Testament, titled "Youthful Worship." Kingston Funeral Home, Westridge Township. Possibly a publisher/printer marketing sample. Copyright (printer?): A. Scheer.
- BH-069. Vintage, circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder BH.069)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of current and early American flags. Gubernatorial campaign in Kansas, promoting Joan Finney for Governor and Jim Francisco for Lt. Governor.
- BH-070. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.070)
  Rounded rectangle. Portrait photograph of formally dressed man captioned Maceo A. Thomas, Jr., Owner. Rollerson & Thomas, Inc. Funeral Home, New York, and the Highbridge Funeral Home, Inc. in the Bronx.
- BH-071. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.071)
  Rounded rectangle. Image of church in tropical setting, urging support for one's community church. Lawrence Sanitary Milk & Ice Cream Co. Printer: Harley J. Scott Co., Kansas City, Missouri.
- BH-072. Vintage, circa 1960 (Box 2, Folder BH.072)
  Rounded rectangle. Line drawing of Jesus as shepherd, with 23rd Psalm. Kirkhoff Funeral Home, Bernville, Pennsylvania. Printer: Hal Roth Adv. Products, Reading, PA.
- BH-073. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.073)
  Rounded rectangle. Line drawing of palm trees, around an open page listing famous Bible passages as "God's Answer to all Problems." Harvey A. Hill, Jr., Funeral Director. Printer: Kennedy & Kennedy Co., Chicago, Illinois. Copy 1, see BH-074.
- BH-074. Vintage (Box 2, Folder BH.074)
  Rounded rectangle. Line drawing of palm trees, around an open page listing famous Bible passages as "God's Answer to all Problems." Harvey A. Hill, Jr., Funeral Director. Printer: Kennedy & Kennedy Co., Chicago, Illinois. Copy 2, see BH-073.
- Inventory and item notes provided by collector Bert Hansen, 2021 (Box 3)
- BH-075. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.075)
  Flat-top oval. Front has a gold design on a royal blue ground that appears to be a monogram, with H & H in gothic lettering. Highbridge/Rollerson and Thomas Funeral Home, Bronx, New York.
- BH-076. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.076)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of flowering shrubs around a lawn in front of a suburban one-story house, titled "An Inviting Setting." Chas. D. Cox, Bricklayer and Builder, and Evelyn's Beauty Shoppe, Bernville, Pennsylvania. Copyright (printer?): A. Scheer; Standard Cal. Co., Madison, Illinois.
- BH-077. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.077)
  Rounded rectangle. Painting of a white-robed Jesus outside a wooden door in a stone building, titled "Christ Knocking at the Door." Copyright (printer?): A. Scheer.
- BH-078. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.078)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photograph of a formal flower arrangement, titled "Rhapsody in Color." Bause's "Super" Drug Stores, in Pottstown and Boyertown. Copyright (printer?): A. Scheer; B. H Bustard, Cedars, Pennsylvania.
- BH-079. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.079)
  Rounded rectangle. Color portrait photograph of a Black man in a pin-striped suit, in front of a paneled wall with a funeral-type flower arrangement partly visible. Likely Ben D. Johnson, noted on the fan as President of Winnfield Funeral Homes, in Natchitoches, Louisiana, with other homes in Louisiana listed.
- BH-080. Vintage, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder BH.080)
  Rounded rectangle. Three portrait photographs of the Black officers of Solomon's Mortuary, Los Angeles, California, and a wide photo of white funeral limos in front of the funeral home.
- BH-081. Vintage (Box 3, Folder BH.081)
  Rounded rectangle. Painted portrait of "Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr." Taylor Funeral Home, Chicago, Illinois. Small photos of Charles B. Taylor and Leyeuna A. Taylor, funeral directors. Copyright (printer?): A. Scheer.
- BH-082. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.082)
  Rounded rectangle. Anti-smoking advocacy from American Association for Respiratory Care. Issued by Grand View Hospital, Respiratory Therapy, Sellersville, Pennsylvania.
- BH-083. Modern, 1987 (Box 3, Folder BH.083)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photograph of Pope John Paul II. Souvenir of the Pope's September 1987 visit to the United States.
- BH-084. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.084)
  Rounded rectangle. Purple image of hands and water ripples. "Lavender Light, The Black and People of All Colors, Lesbian and Gay Gospel Choir."
- BH-085. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.085)
  Outline of Missouri. Issued by Missouri Department of Health. Guidance on handling heat related illness, with lists of other public health services, such as AIDS education, immunizations, etc.
- BH-086. Modern, 1995 (Box 3, Folder BH.086)
  Circle. Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) with slogan "Take Pride, Take Care, Take Action." On back are HIV/AIDS hotline numbers. Copy 1; see BH-87 and BH-88.
- BH-087. Modern, 1995 (Box 3, Folder BH.087)
  Circle. Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) with slogan "Take Pride, Take Care, Take Action." On back are HIV/AIDS hotline numbers. Copy 2; see BH-86 and BH-88.
- BH-088. Modern, 1995 (Box 3, Folder BH.088)
  Circle. Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) with slogan "Take Pride, Take Care, Take Action." On back are HIV/AIDS hotline numbers. Copy 3; see BH-86 and BH-87.
- BH-089. Modern, 1997 (Box 3, Folder BH.089)
  Rounded rectangle. Hamline Church Dining Hall, United Methodist, St. Paul, Minnesota. Fan was distributed at State Fair. Back includes times of Sunday service, including a Hmong service.
- BH-090. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.090)
  Rounded rectangle. Photo of Rev. Cecil Williams and image of congregation. Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California. 30 year celebration of Rev. Cecil Williams, by Pacific Bell.
- BH-091. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.091)
  Rounded rectangle. Ticketmaster publicity for Broadway shows: Disney's Beauty and the Beast, Disney's The Lion King, and Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida.
- BH-092. Modern, 1996 (Box 3, Folder BH.092)
  Rounded rectangle. "We did The Macarena at the 1996 Financial Follies." On back, "How to do it!" (with illustrations), at NYFWA's hospitality suite [NY Financial Writers Association]
- BH-093. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.093)
  Circle. Drawing by Nelson. Chautauqua Opera (western NY summer opera season).
- BH-094. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.094)
  Square. Avian Flyaway, Inc., Bird Relocation Systems.
- BH-095. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.095)
  Rounded rectangle. Publicity for Broadway show "Wicked, A New Musical." Ticket information on back. Copy 1; see BH-96.
- BH-096. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.096)
  Rounded rectangle. Publicity for Broadway show "Wicked, A New Musical." Ticket information on back. Copy 2; see BH-95.
- BH-097. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.097)
  Circle. Operation Lifesaver: Railroad crossing safety, Don't play on bridges, Approach with horse sense not horsepower, Don't throw objects at trains. Printer: Artech Promotional Services, Manhattan, Kansas.
- BH-098. Modern, 1997 (Box 3, Folder BH.098)
  Square. Wildcats (with logo), Kansas State University 1997 football schedule.
- BH-099. Modern, 1997 (Box 3, Folder BH.099)
  Rounded rectangle. Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC). Slogan "Going the distance: Leadership in the fight against AIDS." Pencil note on back: Pride March, NYC, 6-29-97." Copy 1, see BH-100.
- BH-100. Modern, 1997 (Box 3, Folder BH.100)
  Rounded rectangle. Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC). Slogan "Going the distance: Leadership in the fight against AIDS." Pencil note on back: Pride March, NYC, 6-29-97." Copy 2, see BH-99.
- BH-101. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.101)
  Rounded rectangle. Photo of Marilyn Monroe, "I'm a Marilyn Fan."
- BH-102. Modern, circa 1984 (Box 3, Folder BH.102)
  Rounded rectangle. Image of imitation Aunt Jemima. Photo copyright, Bill Bernardo; American Postcard Company.
- BH-103. Modern, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder BH.103)
  Rounded rectangle. "I'm a Fan of Clear Water." Issued by NYC Department of Environmental Protection. Copy 1, see BH-104 and BH-105
- BH-104. Modern, circa 2003 (Box 3, Folder BH.104)
  Rounded rectangle. "I'm a Fan of Clear Water." Issued by NYC Department of Environmental Protection. Copy 2, see BH-103 and BH-105
- BH-105. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.105)
  Rounded rectangle. "I'm a Fan of Clear Water." Issued by NYC Department of Environmental Protection. Copy 3, see BH-103 and BH-104
- BH-106. Modern, 2003 (Box 3, Folder BH.106)
  Circle. Office of the University Chaplain, Columbia University.
- BH-107. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.107)
  Shape of old telephone set. Unclaimed Ca$h [sic], State Treasurer, Kansas.
- BH-108. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.108)
  Hexagonal-like stop sign. Be Tick Free, Sullivan County Public Health, Tick Kit.
- BH-109. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.109)
  Rounded rectangle. Painting of Jesus with sheep, titled "The Good Sheperd." Lutheran Hour Ministries, St. Louis, Missouri. Copyright (printer?): D. Zanone.
- BH-110. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.110)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of Black girl at prayer in a church titled "A Child's Faith." Ransone Funeral Home, Bronx, New York. Copyright (printer?): D. Zanone. Copy 1, see BH-111.
- BH-111. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.111)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of Black girl at prayer in a church titled "A Child's Faith." Ransone Funeral Home, Bronx, New York. Copyright (printer?): D. Zanone. Copy 2, see BH-110.
- BH-112. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.112)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of Black minister holding the hands of a young Black girl, in a church with stained glass windows in background, titled "Divine Wisdom." Ramsay's Funeral Homes, Inc., Liberty, Monticello, and Kauneonga Lake, New York. Copy 1, see BH-113 and BH-114.
- BH-113. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.113)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of Black minister holding the hands of a young Black girl, in a church with stained glass windows in background, titled "Divine Wisdom." Ramsay's Funeral Homes, Inc., Liberty, Monticello, and Kauneonga Lake, New York. Copy 2, see BH-112 and BH-114.
- BH-114. Modern (Box 3, Folder BH.114)
  Rounded rectangle. Color photo of Black minister holding the hands of a young Black girl, in a church with stained glass windows in background, titled "Divine Wisdom." Ramsay's Funeral Homes, Inc., Liberty, Monticello, and Kauneonga Lake, New York. Copy 3, see BH-112 and BH-113.